Did you know there's an awesome
treasure hidden at the end of the sea?
And anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage, have the courage
that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now.
For together we found.
We look through the spyglass and see.
And we know.
That our hearts have brought us here.
Where the conscious points our destiny.
There's no looking back.
Take the hell with me.
Bon voyage.
We can't stop all our troubles.
Forget the past.
Though the future's unclear.
Where we still can smile,
we know we'll get there.
No regrets.
Every tear that we've cried
only helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow?
If you do not wish to be aboard this
ship, there is but one path left for you.
Death.
So long.
There's no way I can
possibly beat this guy.
But I'm not gonna stay on this ship
that's for sure I have no regrets.
Yes I know what you're
thinking and by now I'm
sure you realize you
won't be leaving this arc
safely that is unless
you're pinning your hopes
on those two rats who've
just snuck on board?
Let me off this crazy thing!
Sanji, listen!
If we go any higher, we
won't be able to get down!
Not to mention the fact that God
is on board, or had you forgotten!
We're already here, stupid,
so just deal with it!
But what are we going to do, Sanji?
Look at the size of this thing!
I've seen smaller mountains!
There could be hundreds of guys on board!
We can't fight them all!
Besides, if God or those
priests are here...
Oh, just get over it already.
You're the one who's always
prepared for this kind of stuff.
You got all the cool equipment.
Well, this?
Not what I had in mind when I made them!
Well, the bad guys have
got that mantra ability.
They can predict our moves.
No point in trying to be sneaky.
In fact, I bet my favorite carving
knife they already know we're here.
They know we're here?
So what are we supposed to do?
Stop freaking out for starters.
Once we're safely inside, we'll
split up and head for the main deck.
Nami's got to be up there. Hold on.
Did you say split up?
Are you out of your mind?
Why would we do that?
We have no idea how many
bad guys are on board.
Just getting up here was dangerous enough.
You dumbass.
If we don't split up, we could both die.
Both die?
I don't suppose you care to elaborate.
Wait a minute.
You're not gonna...
You mean to save Nami?
Usopp, listen to me.
If it'll save Nami, I'll gladly sacrifice
your life. You jerk! Why are you on it?
All right, then.
I'm coming, Nami!
I'm gonna get you!
It seems they're quite
serious about your rescue.
Fools to the bitter end!
Who can it be?
No one besides Luffy
can still move Besides,
how could they even get on board the Ark?
Though help may have arrived,
it doesn't mean you've been saved yet,
nor am I obligated to wait for them.
All I can do is jump overboard
and hope for the best.
If I stay here, I'm dead for sure.
I'm up against lightning.
What else can I do?
What's all this?
There's no one here.
But the ship is huge.
Does it run without anyone operating it?
And how does it fly anyway?
I've never heard of a flying ship before.
Just the thought of being up in the air
like this makes my knees all wobbly.
Oh, I feel sick.
I wonder what the power
source for this thing is.
Oh, what do I care?
As long as it doesn't decide to fall.
Wait, I just realized.
Even if Nami is on the upper deck,
we're way too high up now to jump off.
What the hell are we gonna do?
The sky it keeps getting
darker take it up with him.
Onto the boat.
Don't get left behind.
Hurry to the white sea.
We're running out of time.
Look at it.
It's terrifying.
This is really it.
The end of the world.
Leave the village.
But chief.
What about the warriors.
They're still not back from upper yard.
There is no need to wait.
The chief!
We have no choice.
The warriors aren't children.
They can avoid the dangers they face.
Have faith in them.
Enaru will destroy everything.
We know that.
Just as he did to his homeland
Birka, so too shall he do here.
We must escape.
Now, we must prepare the ships.
Our first task is to save the
lives of the villagers here.
Everything is coming to an end.
Wiper, let it go.
You've done everything you could.
Did you come from the Blue Sea World?
If that's what you call it, we sealed
up a river of clouds to get here.
Speaking of here, is this your home?
Everything is happening in this
forest right in front of me,
and I have no way to know what's going on.
All I can do is wait.
Everyone, I hope you're all safe.
Horsie Bird!
Horsie Bird, I'm sorry!
You were trying to protect me!
Aisa!
Luffy?
Are you alive?
Over here!
This way!
Hey! I saw!
Hey!
Help me out!
How did you land like that?
Alright! Dammit!
I can't get this golden ball off!
Hey, watch your mouth!
Let's just get back to that
beanstalk where Robin was!
I won't let Eneru get away with this!
Okay, nice try, jerk, but it
takes a lot more to stop me.
Your arcs toast, and I know
just where to find you?
Congratulations, young lady!
That was rather amusing!
I did it!
Such clever toys you have
down on the Blue Sea.
Thunderbolt!
Creating a path for the
lightning to follow.
A clever tactic.
You're obviously well acquainted
with weather phenomena.
But it's not enough.
You realize, of course, it's futile.
All I need do is raise the voltage
and your trick won't work, will it?
Now I'm a very busy man.
Begone!
Can't dodge this one!
Why don't you be gone?
Exploding star!
Oops, I'm sorry.
Usopp?
I know you.
From the ship.
Hey, where's Sanji? Sanji?
He's here too?
You mean he's not up here yet?
I see.
Later!
Can't see!
Be a man, Usopp.
What are you running for?
Bring it on, God!
Usopp!
Nami! Yeah, what?
Tell me what to do, I'm on it!
Please save me!
What the hell?!
I thought you came here to
save me, you spineless chicken!
Yeah, um, I'm not really
sure what's going on anymore.
Then what are you doing here?!
Well... Well, what?
Get your rear-end gear
and save me right now!
How do I do that exactly?
We are fighting God. Oh, yeah.
By the way, Ami, about that hat.
Yeah, it's Luffy's.
He was here a little while ago,
but Eneru threw him overboard.
But he's not dead, I'm sure of it.
The arc's gaining altitude.
We can't count on Luffy to save us.
Right.
We've got to do this ourselves,
because I'm not a fan of dying.
I'm with you now!
Here, come hide behind this tube thingy.
I'm betting it's pretty important,
so he might not use his big attacks.
Usopp, look over there!
A waver!
We'll have to jump off on that!
Jump from this height? Are you nuts?
No, look!
There's a patch of island cloud
in the middle of the forest!
If we can reach that,
we just might make it!
Of course!
Damn it!
I'll go try to create a
diversion. Get it ready. Right!
Take this, guard!
Behold!
Usopp's spell!
A splinter embeds itself
deep under your fingernail.
That hurts just thinking about it.
Cover your ears, you idiot!
This stuff can kill you!
A piece of paper cuts across
the skin of your knuckles.
Five kankersaurs inflaming your gums!
Usopp, no!
Gotta get this thing running.
We're only gonna get one chance to escape.
Hang on.
Looks good.
The island cloud is directly
below that beanstalk.
Look!
I'm ready!
Let's get...
Usa!
Though you may desperately
want to run away,
facing me, it will not be that simple.
But please, do try it again.
I always enjoy a deadly game of Tang.
Usopp, grab my hand!
Come on!
I'm dead!
For you, there is no hope of salvation.
Usopp!
Get going.
Sanji, run!
Got it, Nami!
Pour!
Uso, wait!
Let off the gas!
What about Sanji?
Don't stop! We gotta escape!
Now stop making my plans sound bad!
And keep going!
So they jumped.
Do they still not understand
the range of my powers?
They haven't escaped me in the slightest.
Hey, God, there's something I
wanted to tell you, but first,
I should thank you.
I was looking for a light.
Appreciate it.
Right.
Do you have a point?
Yeah.
Get ready...
to cry, bastard.
What?
My Ark!
Get ready to cry bastard?
Damn you!
You did something below deck?
What have you done to my ark?
You fool, you wretched fool!
The gears have gone awry!
I must fix them.
Don't you worry.
Nami fell safely into some island clouds.
Usa?
Hoppy!
Oh, no!
We're gonna crash!
We're gonna crash and
then we're gonna die!
AHHHHHHHHHHH!
Dosak! Sanji!
Rami, is that you?
Sounds like you made it down alright.
What a relief.
Sanji, you are a real
- Sanji, are you okay?
You got burnt to a crisp rust.
I'm so sorry.
I promise I'll make it up to you somehow.
Hey, I can't breathe!
I can't breathe! Nami! Sorry!
Hurry up and pull me out!
I can't breathe!
Oh, sorry. All right.
Let's get the heck out of here!
Curse you, Blue Sea Dweller.
This vessel is not so easily brought down.
I am fully acquainted with
the Ark's drive circuits.
We may lack electricity,
but a backup system
harnesses the wind power of
200 jet dials I gathered
in my homeland of Biennale.
They will keep this ship
aloft for quite some time.
No matter what you feeble beings try...
This land and all its pathetic
inhabitants will perish.
Okay, guys, check out that huge vine.
If it's the same one I saw
when I was down in the ruins,
then it stands to reason we're on
the island clouds right above them.
Ruins?
Oh, the City of Gold!
It's real? It's real.
But Enoru took all the gold
that was there for himself.
If the ruins are beneath us, Zoro
and the others should be down there.
I may not know the lay of the land.
But I do know one thing.
Staying here is dangerous.
You got that right. Hop on!
Let's find everyone and
get off this island!
That's a plan.
There are no safe places left in Skypiea.
Luffy, look out!
No!
Wait, Luffy!
That's the wrong way! Go left! Left!
There's no way I can turn that shark!
Gum-gum-pum!
Stop destroying my homeland!
Giant Jack is over that-a-way!
I know, but...
Stop breaking things!
Stop it!
Oh, man.
Robin and the others are gone.
Zoro and Chopper.
And Wiper and Gonefall.
I'm guessing they must
have climbed up already.
Yeah, Robin must have
helped them. Let's go.
Hey, Aisa!
Will the Sky Islands really be destroyed?
Wait for in the others.
They're right through here.
I suspect the ship is moving
towards the Grand Belfry.
Wonder what happened to
Miss Navigator and the boys.
If they're on that ship,
it could mean they're...
We're through!
Ah!
Luffy down there! Stop! Stop!
Robin!
What are you doing?
Look after these two for me!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, stop!
Luffy.
You grew extra hands!
What have you got on your arm?
Robin, the golden bell is at
the top of this vine, right?
And Enneru is trying to get
his hands on it, isn't he?
That's right.
If the Grand Balfry exists,
then the bell would be there.
But he's already good!
Loopy!
So, young lady, have
you seen our navigator?
A woman with orange hair. You mean Nami?
She's on the ship.
I only hear one voice coming from the sky.
Here they are!
Oh, Robin!
Miss Navigator, with long
nose, and the cook, too.
Isa!
Thank goodness, you all right? Nami!
Huh?
Zoro, Chopper, weird
old guy, and a gorilla.
Oh, everyone's been taken down.
Oh, if only I had been here.
Wait, Isa, where's Luffy?
Wasn't he with you?
Luffy climbed up the vine to rescue you.
But since everyone's here, Luffy
has to face Inru by himself.
We missed him, didn't we? Just now.
I tried to stop him,
but he wouldn't lose me.
Damn it, Luffy!
He knows we're running short on time.
We gotta go now!
Go on without me.
I'll take the waiver and find him.
Just try to get to the Mary somehow.
Oh, man!
That ship is moving fast!
In a row!
Quickly, get on the ships!
The whole sky's turning black!
What's wrong?
We need to flee at once.
My daughter, Isa.
She still hasn't...
Ah, she still hasn't returned.
Isa is a bright child.
We must have faith that she is with
some warriors and we'll be protected.
The thunderclouds are
gushing out nicely now.
Hurry! Hurry up!
Captain, if we don't use the boats at
the dock, we'll never fit everyone in.
They'd have to sail all the way around.
You men, use styles to create
rivers inside the island at once.
How many of the islanders are left?
Almost half of them.
People only.
No more baggage.
And get everybody out to
sea right away. Yes, sir.
Hold it.
Nobody's leaving until everyone pays
the $2 billion ex-toll departure fee.
Amazon, hurry!
You can still escape with us! Huh?
Hurry to Cloud End! Huh?
The Sky Islands...
Huh?
...are about to be destroyed!
Oh...
Bye...
The wind has stopped.
Run! Run!
Now then, let us begin the festivities.
The time for endings has come.
Mamaragon.
Get away from the island! Run!
The lightning keeps getting bigger!
The boats at the docks
have been destroyed!
To the western end of the beach!
Quickly!
There's still boats there!
Run to the west!
Move people!
Leave your belongings!
Chief, we need to get you on a boat.
Great warrior Kalgara, I
beg you, protect us all.
Man, those lightning bolts are huge!
We're gonna end up Sky
Dust if we stay here!
Guys, go now!
Once I find Bloopie,
we'll be right behind you!
Uh, yeah, right. I gotcha.
Hurry, Robin.
We gotta find a way to carry
these guys to the ship.
Wiper!
Swordsman.
Weird old guy!
Oh good, you're awake now.
There's not a moment to lose.
Do you think you can walk yet?
So...
Energo has begun.
We must all hurry now.
There is truly nothing
more we can do here.
Viper...
We have to get out of here!
Not even Luffy can handle
an enemy who can fly!
I have to get to him before
this island is obliterated!
Magnificent!
You better not think for a second that I'm
gonna let you get away with this in a row!
When you're lost and alone,
I can always hear your voice.
While you wander far from
home, gazing up at the sky.
You are just like the moon,
you never change as you
climb into the night.
But your reflection wanes,
then you disappear fading so silently.
Stay as you are.
Don't lose your way.
Let these words guide you.
Don't ever look back.
Don't give up on your dreams.
They're windless nights.
They come to you again and again.
Until you see the journey through.
You may not return, I
hope that you'll learn.
To put your past behind,
and just keep moving on.